Guide to the Yale Course Lectures Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale course lectures collection
1720-1989
RU 159
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
83.128
(183 boxes)
The collection consist of notes on course lectures taken by Yale students.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 47 (YRG 47), Collections documenting teaching and learning in Yale academic programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research. Portions of the collection cannot be duplicated due to fragility of materials. See collection contents for details.
Existence and Location of Copies
Notes of Laurence Hewes on Josiah W. Gibbs's lectures are available on microfilm (70 frames on 1 reel, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM114. Notes on Dr. Eli Ives's and Dr. William Tully's lectures are available on microfilm (1404 frames on 3 reels, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM165.
Scope and Contents
The collection consist of notes on course lectures taken by Yale students.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Lecture notes; Lectures; Gibbs, J. Willard (Josiah Willard), 1839-1903; Ives, Eli, 1779-1861; Tully, William, 1785-1859; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Faculty; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students
- Yale lecture notes, 1833-1965; Accession 19ND-A-393
  - Finch, Edward Ridley, 1873-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Three class notebooks on European History, 1895, English Constitutional History, 1895, and Psychology, ca.1895. One paperbound biographical book about E.R.Finch, Judicial Politics by Edward R. Finch, Jr., 1966.
  - Lowe, Orton (Box 1, Folder 2)
    One notebook kept the summer of 1907 for a novel. course taught by Wilbur Cross and for American Literature taught by Henry Beers.
  - Brewster, Chauncey Bunce (1868 Yale College) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notebook
  - Hazard, Vincent G. (1874 Yale College) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Two notebooks on Political History of the United States (1874?). Two notebooks of Constltutional History of the United States (1873?). One notebook with Roman History (1868) and Latin Prose composition (1871).
  - Livingston, Beverly (1874 Sheffield), 1873-1874 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Zoology notebook with notes about a European trip.
  - Leavitt, Johnathan, 1820 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notebook "Examples in the delectable Science of Mensuration."
  - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Law notes
  - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Psychology notes
  - Williams, Frederick W., ex 1890s (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Conditions Governing Access
    2 notebooks of mechanical drawings
  - Harris, Franklin S. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Physics experiment papers
  - Harris, Franklin S., 1932 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Mechanical drawings
  - Beadle, Delos White, (1844 Yale College), circa 1844 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes and essays on English History and Religion
  - Clapp, Lowell L. (?) (1876 Yale College), 1875 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notebook on Chemistry, German, Greek and Political Economy
  - Merrow, R.G. (?) (1909 Yale College), 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notebook of Physics Experiments
  - Merrow, R.G. (?) (1909 Yale College) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Notebook on Geography of.South America (Professor Bowman)
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Notebook on English Constitutional History (Prof.R.M. Smith), Administrative Law (Professor Goodnow) and General Constitutional History (Professor Burgess) Columbia Law School.
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College), 1888 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notebook on Constitutional History Columbia Law School
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Law Notebook - Blackstone and Parsons on Contracts Columbia Law School
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Law Notebook - Parsons on Contracts Columbia Law School.
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Notebook on Constitutional Law and Torts Columbia Law School
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College), 1888 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Notebook on Real Property and History of Diplomacy Columbia Law School
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Notebook on Socialism
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Notebook on Medieval History and Political Economy
  - Tracy, Howard Crosby (1887 Yale College) (Box 4, Folder 25A)
    Notebook on English Constitutional History and European History
  - Seymour, Morris W.Y. (1866 Yale College) (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Law Notebook 1864-66 Columbia Law School (?)
  - Marsh, George Tracy (1898 Yale College), 1898-1900 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Notebook on Property Harvard Law School
  - Baldwin, Nathan Clark (?) (1837 M.D.) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Notebook on medical cures (possibly materia medica)
  - Stevens, Shepard (1922 M.A.), 1906? (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Architecture Sketchbook
  - Patton, Robert Brooks (1817 Yale College), 1833-1836 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Diary and Notebook on Greek
  - Patton, Robert Brooks? (1817 Yale College) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 32)
    German Translations (Professor Carver)
  - Bishop, Ernest S. (1889 Yale College) (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Notebook of Chemistry Experiments
  - Bishop, Ernest S. (1889 Yale College) (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Notebook on Chemistry, Law, American History, European History and Psychology
  - Beach, John S. (1839 Yale College), 1842 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Notebook on Law, Latin, miscellany and some records of the Yale Law School Debating Society
  - Seymour, Thomas D. (1870 Yale College), 1871-1872 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    2 envelopes of notes Germany
  - Seymour, Thomas D. (1870 Yale College), 1871-1872 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    (1st) 9 (out of 18) notebooks Germany
  - Seymour, Thomas D. (1870 Yale College), 1871-1872 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    (2nd) 9 (out of 18) notebooks Germany
  - Phelps, William Lyon (1887 Yale College), 1889, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Notebook on English Literature (from outside sources) (Professor Beer) 1889; and English Drama (Mr. Baker) Harvard University 1891
  - Ingersoll, James W.D. (1892 Yale College), 1893 October (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Attic Inscriptions
    - Calculus vol. I (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Calculus vol. II (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Calculus vol. IIII (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Catullus [optional work], 1890 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Catullus (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Cicero's Letters vol. I (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Cicero's Letters vol. II (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Demosthenes, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Greek Archeology, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Greek Dialects vol. I, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Greek Dialects vol. II, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Greek Etymology, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      Professor Thomas D. Goodell
    - Philosophy, 1892 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Greek Testament, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Professor Edward Clapp
    - Greek Theatre vol. I, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Greek Theatre vol. II, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Latin Philology
    - Greek Tragedy, 1891-1892 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      Professor Thomas D. Seymour
    - Hebrew (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Textual criticism [Cicero's Orations], 1894 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      Professor Edward Morris
    - Herodotus (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Thucydides (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Gorgias of Plato, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Historic Syntax, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Homer (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Homer (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Sanskrit, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      Professor William D. Whitney
    - Isaeus [Greek Orators], 1892 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Italic Dialects vol. I, 1896-1897 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      Professor Hans Oertel
    - Italic Dialects vol. I, 1897 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Latin Prose, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Professor Tracy Peck
    - Dialogues of Tacitus, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Latin, Low vol. I (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - German Language and Literature (Box 11, Folder 66)
      Professor Gustav Gruener
    - English Romanticism, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      Professor Henry Beers
    - Latin, Low vol. II (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Phaedo (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Latin Philology, 1895-1896 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Greek Private Life [Antiquity], 1895 (Box 11, Folder 68)
      Professor Bernadette Perrin
    - Linguistics vol. I (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Linguistics vol. II (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Old English (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Latin, Early (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Logic and Moral Philosophy (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Lucretius, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Medieval History vol. I, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      Professor George Adams
    - Medieval History vol. II, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Political Economy, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 74)
      Professor Arthur Hadley
    - Herodotus, 1896-1897 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Philosophy, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 75)
      Professor George Ladd
    - Physics [Optics] (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Plautus vol. I, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Plautus vol. II (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Plautus: Menachmi (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Pliny, 1893 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Psychology, Outlines of Psychology, vol. I., James Sully, M.A. (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Psychology, Outlines of Psychology, James Sully, M.A. (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Outlines of Laws of Thought, Thomson (Box 13, Folder 82)
      General note
      Folders 81 and 82 contain Ingersoll's handwritten copies of psychology textbooks.
    - Roman Satire, 1891 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Persius, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Satire and Comedy (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Spanish, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      Professor Henry Lang
    - Phonetics, 1896 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Tacitus (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Roman Satire (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Latin Composition, 1891 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Theocritus (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Lucretius (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Lucan (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Flora (Greek) (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Havens, Franke (1896 Yale College)
    - Chemistry (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Roman History (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Greek Composition (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Optics (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - "Dr. Gooche's actual lecture notes used in Laboratory 1895" [and 1897] (Box 14, Folder 90)
      [Frank A. Gooch -- Chemistry]
    - Biblical Literature ["senior year"] (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Biblical Literature (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Biblical Literature (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Mineralogical Laboratory [Sheffield Scientific School] (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Kimball, Chase (1925 Yale College)
    - Mathematics [number -20, division 2] (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Adams, Alexander B. (1939 Yale College)
    - English notes with examinations, 1936-1939? (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - English notes, 1936-1939? (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - English Drama notes, 1939? (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Confrancesco, Harry W. (1926 Yale College)
    - Anatomy, laboratory sketchbook, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Chemistry, laboratory notebook and workbook (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - French, workbook (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Mathematics, workbooks (2), 1922 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Mathematics, workbooks (2) (solid geometry), 1923 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Barnum, Samuel W. (1841? Yale College), Algebra notes, 1835-1836 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - McConoughy, Donald, (1912 Yale College): notebooks Nineteenth Century Poets "T and B" [Tennyson and Browning] (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - New England Writers; History of Music (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Advanced French Prose Composition, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Solutions to problems and exercises in Granville text, circa 1905 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Class notes from course in Thermodynamics, circa 1905 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - John Gordon (1923 Yale College), 2 volumes of History of Art notes, circa 1923 (Box 17, Folder 110-111)
  - Notes of Robert A. Heller fiom Engineering Materials taught by Henry A. Lepper and General Engineering taught by Thomas G. Looney, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 112-113)
- Yale lectures, 1720-1980; Accession 19ND-A-394
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., 1899-1900 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notetaker: Wilson, Edwin B. (1901 Graduate School)
    Subject: Mathematics; Physics
  - Phelps, William Lyon., 1908-1909 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notetaker: Warren, Harvey T. (1910 Yale College)
    Subject: English
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notetaker: Dodd, Edward L. (1902 Yale College)
    Subject: Mathematics
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Subject: Physics
  - Hitchcock, Samuel J., 1828 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notetaker: Merwin, Timothy T. (1827 Yale College)
    Subject: Law
  - Day, Jeremiah., undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notetaker: Carpenter, E. W. (1868 Yale College)
    Subject: Philosophy
  - Day, Jeremiah., 1812-1813 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notetaker: Olmsted, Denison. (1813 Yale College)
  - Day, Jeremiah., 1807-1808 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notetaker: Tyler, Septimius. (1808 Yale College)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1810 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notetaker: Vaill, Joseph. (1811 Yale College)
    Subject: Chemistry
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1819-1820 (Box 110)
    Notetaker: Abbe, Alanson. (1821 Yale School of Medicine)
  - unknown, 1904-1905 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notetaker: Hewes, Lawrence Ilsley. (1901 Yale College)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., 1899-1900 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., 1899-1900 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., 1899-1900 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pierpont, James., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Smith, P. F., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Smith, P. F., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Smith, P. F., 1899 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Smith, P. F., 1903, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Chittenden, Russell., 1891-1892 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Notetaker: Williams, Charles M. (1892 Sheffield)
  - Verriel, A. E., 1881 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Notetaker: Lambert, Samuel W. (1880 Yale College)
    Subject: Biology
  - Wheeler, Arthur M., 1880 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Notetaker: Wheeler, Frank H. (1880 Yale College)
    Subject: History
  - Wilson, Edwin B., 1900-01 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Wilson, Edwin B., 1902 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Harris, Samuel., 1860s (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Notetaker: Lewis, George.
    Subject: Theology
  - Day, Jeremiah., 1809-10 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Notetaker: Thomson, Asahel. (1810 Yale College)
  - Day, Jeremiah., 1814 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Notetaker: Woodhull, Jesse S. (1815 Yale College)
  - Eggleston, Sir Frederick., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Notetaker: Unknown.
    Subject: INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS
  - Ruml, Beardsley., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Subject: Business
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1833 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Notetaker: Adams, Ebenezer B. (1835 Yale College)
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1834 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Subject: Astronomy
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1828-29 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Notetaker: Boardman, John F. (1829 Yale College)
    Subject: Astronomy; Philosophy
  - Phelps, William Lyon., 1895 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Notetaker: Cott, Charles. (1896 Yale College)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Elder., 1808 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Notetaker: Daggett, David L. (1808 Yale College)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Elder., 1807 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Cameron, Alastair G. W., 1962-63 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Subject: Astronomy; Physics
  - Cameron, Alastair G. W., 1963-64 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Cameron, Alastair G. W., 1964-65 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Dudley, Samuel W., 1923-24 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    Subject: Engineering
  - Dudley, Samuel W., 1927-28 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Dudley, Samuel W., 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Dudley, Samuel W., 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Adams, John C., 1922-23 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    Notetaker: Evans, Oliver. (1923 Yale College)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1922-23 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1923? (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1923? (Box 11, Folder 47)
    Subject: Art
  - Keller, Albert G., 1921-22 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    Subject: Anthropology
  - Davie, Maurice R., 1922-23 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Westerfield, Ray B., 1921-22 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    Subject: Economics
  - Furniss, Edgar S., 1921-22 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Fairchild, Frederick R., 1921-22 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Westerfield, Ray B., 1922-23 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Duncan, George M., 1922-23 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Angier, Roswell P., 1921-22 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    Subject: Psychology
  - Eberhard, Robert G., 1927-28 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    Notetaker: Hogan, Charles B. (1928 Yale College)
  - French, Robert Dudley., 1926-27 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Keller, Albert G., 1926-27 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    Subject: SOCIOLOGY
  - Nettleton, George H., 1926-27 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Simonds, Bruce., 1927-28 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    Subject: MUSIC
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1927-28 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Witherspoon, Alexander., 1927-28 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Williams, Stanley T., 1926-27 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Kingsley, James L., 1827[?] (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Notetaker: Lewis, John N.[?]. (1828 Yale College?)
    Subject: Languages
  - Day, George E.[?].; Bacon, Leonard.; Dwight, Timothy., 1873 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Notetaker: Peck, Marshall R.[?]. (1875 Yale College)
  - Bacon, Leonard.; Day, George E.[?].; Davies?., 1874 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Fisher, George P., 1874-75 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Fisher, George P., 1873-74 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Porter, Charles T., 1914 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Percy F., 1917 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
    Notetaker: Waring, James J. (1850 Yale College)
  - Bacon, Leonard., undated (Box 14, Folder 72)
    Notetaker: Goodrich, Chauncey. (1837 Yale College)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1841 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Silliman, Benjamin?., 1810 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    Notetaker: Baldwin, Hezekiah H. (1810 Yale College)
    Subject: Chemistry; Geology
  - Dwight, Timothy, Elder., 1809 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1810 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    Subject: Geology
  - Unknown., 1809-10 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Unknown., 1809-10 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Unknown., 1810 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Beers, Henry A., 1888 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    Notetaker: Bradner, Lester. (1889 Yale College)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Elder., 1816 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    Notetaker: Bird, Isaac. (1816 Yale College)
    Subject: English; Philosophy; Theology
  - Unknown., 1912[?] (Box 15, Folder 80)
    Notetaker: Brewer, Henrietta.
    Subject: Classics
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., undated (Box 15, Folder 81)
    Notetaker: Birdseye, Lucien. (1841 Yale College)
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1840 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Fisher, Alexander M., 1820 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    Notetaker: Case, William. (1821 Yale College)
  - Unknown., 1818 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    Subject: English.
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1820 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Harris, Samuel., undated (Box 15, Folder 85)
    Notetaker: Clapp, Lowell L. (1876 Yale College)
  - Unknown., undated (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 87)
    Notetaker: Bull, Ludlow.
    Subject: Egyptology
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Bull, Ludlow., 1924-1935? (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Younger., 1885-86 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Daggett, Leonard M., undated (Box 17, Folder 95)
    Notetaker: Daggett, Leonard M.
  - Daggett, Leonard M., undated (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Day, George E., 1877 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    Notetaker: Bird, George H.
  - Day, Jeremiah., 1815 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    Notetaker: Unknown
  - Bacon, Leonard., 1837 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    Notetaker: Day, George E. (1833 Yale College)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1836 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Elder., 1816 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Harris, Samuel., 1883 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    Notetaker: Elderdice, Hugh L. (1890 Yale College)
  - Fisher, George P., 1889 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Fisher, George P., 1890 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Harris, Samuel., 1882 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Dwight, Timothy., 1883 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Fisher, George P., 1883 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Younger., 1882 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Harris, Samuel., 1884 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Younger., 1883 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1839-40 (Box 19, Folder 110)
    Notetaker: Fitch, Eleazar T.
  - Morton, Charles., 1720-21 (Box 19, Folder 111)
    Notetaker: Heath, Peleg. (1721 Yale College)
  - Walker, Francis A., undated (Box 19, Folder 112)
    Notetaker: Hazard, Vincent G. (1874 Yale College)
  - Walker, Francis A., undated (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., undated (Box 19, Folder 114)
    Notetaker: Goodrich, Chauncey A.
  - Emery, Henry C., 1903 (Box 20, Folder 115A)
    Notetaker: Emery, Henry C.
  - Emery, Henry C., 1904 (Box 20, Folder 115B)
  - Emery, Henry C., 1904 (Box 20, Folder 115C)
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1828-29 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    Notetaker: Hough, Alfred. (1830 Yale College)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Kingsley, James L., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Stuart, Moses. [Andover Sem.]., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1828 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1828 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - unknown, 1852 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Lewis, Charlton M., 1905 (Box 20, Folder 119)
    Notetaker: Porter, Delia Lyman.
  - Mason, Max., 1906-07 (Box 21, Folder 120)
    Notetaker: Mason, Max.
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1843 (Box 21, Folder 121)
    Notetaker: Merwin, Samuel J. M. (1839 Yale College)
  - Packard, Lewis R., undated (Box 21, Folder 122)
    Notetaker: Packard, Lewis R. (1856 Yale College)
  - Packard, Lewis R., undated (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Packard, Lewis R., undated (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Packard, Lewis R., undated (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Pierpont, James., undated (Box 22, Folder 126)
    Notetaker: Pierpont, James.
  - Porter, Milton B., 1899-1900 (Box 22, Folder 127)
    Notetaker: Porter, Milton B.
  - Porter, Milton B., 1901-02 (Box 22, Folder 128)
  - Porter, Noah., 1867-68 (Box 23, Folder 129)
    Notetaker: Gaines, Marshall R. (1865 Yale College)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight., 1857-58 (Box 23, Folder 130)
    Notetaker: Scott, E. Greenough. (1858 Yale College)
    Subject: History; Philosophy
  - Seymour, Morris W., undated (Box 24, Folder 131)
    Notetaker: Seymour, Morris W.
  - Seymour, Morris W., 1892-94[?] (Box 24, Folder 132)
    Notetaker: Seymour, Morris W. (1866 Yale College)
  - Seymour, Morris W., 1892-94[?] (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1825 (Box 25, Folder 134)
    Notetaker: Townsend, Isaac. (1822 Yale College)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1818 (Box 25, Folder 135)
    Notetaker: Tracy, J. Charles.
  - Smith, Percy F., 1901-02 (Box 26, Folder 136)
    Notetaker: Smith, Percy F.
  - Smith, Percy F., 1899-1900 (Box 27, Folder 137)
  - Unknown., 1820-22 (Box 28, Folder 138)
    Notetaker: Smith, E. Goodred. (1822 Yale College)
  - Smith, Percy F., 1900-01 (Box 28, Folder 139)
  - Smith, Percy F., 1903-04 (Box 28, Folder 140)
  - Starkweather, George P., 1900-01 (Box 29, Folder 141)
    Notetaker: Starkweather, George P.
  - Sumner, William G., 1875 (Box 29, Folder 142)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1845-46 (Box 29, Folder 143)
    Notetaker: Mershon, James R. (1844 Yale College)
  - Bacon, Leonard., 1843 (Box 29, Folder 144)